# Manasa Koppal



manasa.koppal13@gmail.com +919480992162

# SKILLS AND PROFICIENCIES

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React
- · ServiceNow tool
- Incident management, request management and knowledge management.
- Strong communication skills in English, Hindi and Kannada.
- Strong interpersonal & relationship building
- Active listening and talented customer service
- Ability to work in a team environment, which may be local, global, virtual, or multifunctional
- Ability to multi-task and make sound judgments in a fastpaced, high stress environment.

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Diligent System engineer with 2 years of experience in Tata Consultancy Services. Looking for a challenging position, applying creative problem solving and learn management skills with a growing company to achieve optimum utilization of all the resources and thus targeting it's growth and myself as well.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **System Engineer**

Tata Consultancy Services | July 2020- Present

- My prime responsibilities include monitoring website performance and rectifying front-end related issues.
- Developed user-friendly website, fixed bugs from existing websites and implemented enhancements that significantly improved web functionality and speed.
- Collaborated with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.

### **Assistant System Engineer**

Tata Consultancy Services | June 2019 - June 2020

- Worked as a part of ITIL Access Management team. Access Management works closely with information security management to ensure that the access provisions of the information security policy are enforced.
- creation of a process document, standard procedures and knowledge documents.
  Maintaining a catalog of user roles and access profiles and provisioning user access requests.
- Requests for access are initiated as service requests and are handled by us for fulfillment.
- Managing the request fulfillment process and identifying opportunities to optimize the workflow via continuous improvement initiative.
- Monitored ServiceNow training instance, provided training to new joiners regarding knowledge, incident, problem and request management.
- Achieved recognition and appreciation from customers for my speed, simplicity, delivery, authenticity and performance.

# Manasa Koppal

## **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

B.E. Electrical and Electronic Engineering Basaveshwar Engineering College, Bagalkot | 2015 -19 8.3 CGPA

XII

Kittur Rani Channamma Residential Sainik School for Girls, Kittur, Karnataka | 2014 - 15 85 %

Χ

Kittur Rani Channamma Residential Sainik School for Girls, Kittur, Karnataka | 2012 - 2013 87.36 %

## **HOBBIES AND INTERESTS**

- Reading books (Philosophical, spiritual, motivational and fiction novels).
- · Sports Badminton, Marathon running
- Passionate dancer and singer.
- · Listening to music and podcasts.